I just got here and I think I'm losing
signal already
hello can you hear me now
sorry I'm
not sorry
[Music]
hello it's
me I was wondering if after all the
these years you'd like to me to go
over
everything they say the time supposed to
heal you but I ain't done much
healing
hello can you hear
me I'm in California Dreaming of about
who we used to be when we were younger
and
free I forgotten how it felt before the
world fell our feet there's such a
difference between us and the
milon
miles H from the other
side I must have called a th
to tell you I'm sorry for everything
that I've done but when I call you
never seem to
behold H from the
outside at least I can see that I'm
try to tell you I'm so sorry for
breaking your heart but it don't matter
he
clearly doesn't take you aart
[Music]
anymore
hello how are
you it's so typical let me to talk about
myself I'm sorry I hope
let you
wh did you ever make it out of that town
where nothing ever happened it's no
secret that the both of us are running
out of
town so hell from the other
side I'm must I've called a thousand
times to tell you I'm sorry for
everything that I've done but when I
call you
never seem to be
home H from the
outside at least I can see that I'll
try to tell you oh I'm
sorry for breaking your heart but it
don't matter it
clearly doesn't take you apart
anymore any
from the other
side I must have called a thousand
times to tell you I'm sorry for
everything that I've done but when I
call you
never seem to be home
H from the
outside at least I can think that I'm
try to tell you I'm
stor the breaking your heart but it
don't matter
clearly doesn't tell you apart and need
more
[Music]